<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lotus Docs Example Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Lotus Docs Example Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 07:07:07 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/docs/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Don - Monster Kingdom Building Fantasy LitRPG Journey Novel</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/books/collapsed/don/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/books/collapsed/don/</guid>
      <description>The book cover presents a vibrant scene reminiscent of a classic role-playing game. A charming, red-roofed building, likely an inn or shop, sits atop a floating island with a pathway leading down to a lower level. Several characters, including a young woman with red attire, populate the scene. Red triangles with exclamation points hover above the characters, suggesting alerts or warnings within the game&amp;rsquo;s context. In the bottom left corner, a red goblin icon with the text &amp;ldquo;x3&amp;rdquo; indicates a potential threat or enemy encounter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John the Traitor</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/books/collapsed/john/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/books/collapsed/john/</guid>
      <description>⚠️ Novel Under Construction ⚠️ linkThis novel is a work in progress and may undergo changes. Sections may be incomplete or subject to revisions. Thank you for your patience and understanding!&#xA;A man named John with dark hair and a stern expression stands at the center of the cover. He wears a regal purple robe, indicating nobility or magical prowess, and grips a sword with determination. Behind him looms a menacing landscape with twisted trees, shadowy figures, and a distant, ominous castle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Katherine: Delicate Path - Ascension to Godhood Isekai Novel</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/books/collapsed/katherine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/books/collapsed/katherine/</guid>
      <description>⚠️ Novel Under Construction ⚠️ linkThis novel is a work in progress and may undergo changes. Sections may be incomplete or subject to revisions. Thank you for your patience and understanding!&#xA;A woman with flowing purple hair and a determined expression holds a hand to her face, which is partially obscured by a swirling mass of purple energy and shattering crystals. The background is a dark purple, and the title &amp;ldquo;Katherine&amp;rdquo; is written in a bold, gothic font above the subtitle &amp;ldquo;Delicate Path - Ascension to Godhood Isekai Novel&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark: Tainted Ambition - Sociopath LitRPG Fantasy Novel</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/books/collapsed/mark/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/books/collapsed/mark/</guid>
      <description>A menacing figure named Mark, radiating an aura of power and danger, takes center stage on the book cover. He is cloaked in darkness with a black hood and a sinister mask featuring a glowing red cross and a chilling smile. A black pillar rises behind him, adding to the atmosphere of intimidation. Streaks of red and orange emanate from Mark, suggesting a supernatural or corrupt energy. The background remains relatively muted and atmospheric, allowing the focus to stay on the imposing figure and the vibrant colors associated with him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew: The Epitome of Grace and Beauty - An Intellectual Psychological Isekai LitRPG</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/books/collapsed/matthew/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/books/collapsed/matthew/</guid>
      <description>A man named Matthew with dark hair and a smirk stands on a rooftop, extending his hand toward the viewer as if inviting them in. He&amp;rsquo;s dressed in elegant, dark clothing with a pop of color from a red-orange undershirt. The background is a city at night, bathed in cool blue tones with buildings silhouetted against the sky. The title, &amp;ldquo;Matthew,&amp;rdquo; is written in a bold, white, handwritten font at the bottom of the image.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peter: In the Maelstrom&#39;s Embrace</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/books/collapsed/peter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/books/collapsed/peter/</guid>
      <description>⚠️ Novel Under Construction ⚠️ linkThis novel is a work in progress and may undergo changes. Sections may be incomplete or subject to revisions. Thank you for your patience and understanding!&#xA;A lone figure named Peter, cloaked in black and wielding a glowing sword, stands defiantly against a backdrop of swirling chaos. The scene is filled with fiery oranges and blues, depicting a cosmic maelstrom of energy and destruction. The title &amp;ldquo;Peter&amp;rdquo; is boldly displayed in a striking orange font with a black outline, demanding attention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Santo: Rattle &amp; Craft - An Isekai LitRPG of Bones and Business</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/books/collapsed/santo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/books/collapsed/santo/</guid>
      <description>A skeletal figure, draped in a purple robe, stands behind a market stall filled with jars and containers of various goods. The figure&amp;rsquo;s bony hand gestures towards the merchandise, suggesting a merchant or vendor. The setting appears to be an open-air marketplace with a simple cloth awning providing shade. The title, &amp;ldquo;Santo,&amp;rdquo; is prominently displayed in a stylized, gray font with a slight drop shadow, giving it a whimsical yet slightly eerie feel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skylet - Schizoid Isekai Journey Novel</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/books/collapsed/skylet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/books/collapsed/skylet/</guid>
      <description>A young man with white hair walks confidently towards the viewer, flanked by two girls with long, flowing hair in contrasting shades of pink and white. They stand on a grassy cliff edge overlooking a breathtaking fantasy landscape bathed in ethereal light, suggesting a magical journey or adventure. The title, &amp;ldquo;Skylet,&amp;rdquo; is written below in a playful, white, bubble-letter font, adding a sense of whimsy. Underneath, the tagline &amp;ldquo;Schizoid Isekai Journey&amp;rdquo; is presented in a simple, white sans-serif font, hinting at the story&amp;rsquo;s themes and genre.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/books/collapsed/antipoloa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/books/collapsed/antipoloa/</guid>
      <description>Chapter 1 - Laborer link Author&amp;rsquo;s Note&#xA;Stay and rest awhile. This is going to be a long ride. I may fine-tune published chapters as I go, but the main idea is there: how limited one narration is yet how wide everyday actions influence society. I am narratively restoring the power back to the people by emphasizing how much power an individual holds amid war and terror. It&amp;rsquo;s third person omniscient point of view, so be warned.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
